A Guide to the Evans Family Papers 1709-1928
Library of Virginia
- Series V. Oversized Items (Box Box 22-24)
  - Stock Certificate - Downingstown, Ephrata and Harrisburg Turnpike Road, 1803 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Subscription List - Relief for Citizens of Savannah, 1820 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Supplee Steam Engine Company (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Tavern Licenses (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Title Abstracts (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Series VI. Framed Items (Box Box 25)
  The framed items include a letter from David Jones of Philadelphia to Brig. Gen. William Irvine of Carlisle, Pennsylvania, dated 20 April 1781, as well as a deed from David Powell to James Parry, dated 28 October 1709.
  - Letter, David Jones (Chaplain), Philadelphia, to Brig. Gen. William Irvine, Carlisle, 20 April 1781 (Box 25, Folder n/a)
  - Deed, David Powell to James Parry, 28 October 1709 (Box 25, Folder n/a)
- Series VII. Ledger
  The ledger contains miscellaneous papers that were professional conserved prior to their donation to The Library of Virginia. A decision was made to leave the ledger intact, rather than split up its contents. It includes various wills and estate inventories of members of the Evans and Davis families, correspondence between John D. Evans and Edward Livingston (Evans), Bible records, genealogical notes, and other material.